UTAGE: Tamon-kun! Tamon-kun!
TAMON: What is it, Utage-chan?
UTAGE: Why are you just so cool, Tamon-kun?
TAMON: Why else?
TAMON: It's to make you fall for me.
UTAGE: Yeah, I'mma die!
UTAGE: Tamon-kun...
UTAGE: A dream.
SIGN: Commemorating F/ACE OFF's Release
SIGN: F/ACE Meet-and-Greet Ticket
SIGN: Tamon Fukuhara
SIGN: 20XX.X.X (Sat)
Tokyo: TOKYO Hall
UTAGE: Or not.
UTAGE: Th-This is reality!
YAMATO: Nee-chan, shut up! It's still early!
LYRICS: Hey!! It's just like sweeet magic!! Aha!
LYRICS: Hi, it's me!
The one with that killer smile!
LYRICS: Stealing your gaze with a shocking style!
LYRICS: Smooth as ever, I escort you
LYRICS: And this voice, seducing you
LYRICS: Ah, come on, let's dance;
I'm aiming straight for your heart
LYRICS: I am your ace darlin'
LYRICS: Confidence? Yeah, I've got plenty
LYRICS: Please Please
LYRICS: Whisper just to me, call my name
LYRICS: You're too popular,
it drives me crazy and I'm not okay
LYRICS: But I'm sorry, losing's not my thing
LYRICS: Hey, girl
LYRICS: Look this way!
LYRICS: I see your smile, smile, smile,
I wanna make it all mine
LYRICS: Crash, crash, crash,
our special connection shines
LYRICS: Dance, dance,
our world is non-stop groovin'
LYRICS: I'll show you my perfect
A-side, side, side
LYRICS: And my private B-side, side, side;
I'll show you everything
LYRICS: So take my hand and let's roll
LYRICS: Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
LYRICS: Sweetie honey Sweetie honey
LYRICS: It's a spell that makes your heart race
LYRICS: We can't go back
LYRICS: You're falling in love with me, c'mon!
LYRICS: Sweetie honey
LYRICS: Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
SIGN: Do You Like Me?
UTAGE: Yahoo!
UTAGE: F/ACE has been known to be
on the artistic side of this industry,
UTAGE: but they're finally having
a fan interaction event!
UTAGE: It was totally worth spending my
life savings to pile up on those CDs!
UTAGE: I'm gonna have to scrub down
my body extra hard.
UTAGE: I need to buy some new clothes, too!
UTAGE: I need to start working my butt off
for that meet-and-greet!
UTAGE: That's right...
UTAGE: Hello, Fukuhara-sama.
UTAGE: I look forward to working
with you again tod...
UTAGE: ...as Tamon-kun's housekeeper.
TAMON: I'm gonna retire! Please don't look for me!
FUJITA: Quit whining and get to work!
FUJITA: How much do you think
the agency has invested in you?!
FUJITA: Damn it! How am I supposed to babysit
these five brats all on my own?!
FUJITA: Yes, hello?!
UTAGE: O-Oh, hello...
FUJITA: Ouri, where are you right now?!
FUJITA: Don't forget we're on location tomorrow!
UTAGE: Fukuhara-san...
UTAGE: What did you mean by retire?
MUSHROOM: Gloom.
TAMON: They've gone and scheduled a meet-and-greet...
TAMON: I'm so nervous, I-I might throw up.
UTAGE: It's an extremely rare opportunity
to see your smiling fans up close.
UTAGE: You want to make everyone
in the world smile, don't you?
TAMON: That's just impossible, though!
TAMON: If I have to directly communicate
with hundreds of people,
TAMON: I'm definitely going to slip up!
TAMON: They'll know I'm all gloom-and-doom!
TAMON: My sweaty hands'll gross 'em out and make 'em
say, "Whoa, mushroom farm (lol)."
TAMON: It makes no sense for the confident, cool guy
to have sweat glands on his palms!
TAMON: Also what the hell is "sexy and wild"
even supposed to mean?!
TAMON: What's so good about a guy who could be
arrested for sexual harassment at any time?!
TAMON: What is wrong with people using their life
savings to buy up CDs for a guy like him?!
UTAGE: Hello? Tamon-kun's hand sweat
is literally elixir.
UTAGE: Hello? Being able to breathe the same air
as Tamon-kun is a delicious meal.
UTAGE: Hello?!
TAMON: Peep!
UTAGE: Don't put sexual harassment and
sexy and wild in the same category!
SIGN: Church of Tamon
UTAGE: It's written as "world peace"
but read as "sexy and wild."
SIGN: World Peace
SIGN: Wild
SIGN: Sexy &
TAMON: I'm so sorry...
SIGN: World Peace
SIGN: Sexy & Wild
SIGN: Church of Ta
UTAGE: I almost pushed him down again.
UTAGE: I mean...
UTAGE: Yeah, Hottiehara-san's hotness
is on another dimensional level.
UTAGE: But you're charming in your
own way, Gloomyhara-san!
TAMON: If I'm going to do this, I want to do it right.
TAMON: There'll be people coming
to see me with high hopes,
TAMON: so I want to do everything I can.
UTAGE: In that case...
UTAGE: Here's two years' worth.
UTAGE: Magazine interviews, blogs,
and internet articles I saved and filed.
UTAGE: And over here, I wrote down
everything you said on TV,
UTAGE: the internet, videos, and social media.
UTAGE: This is my sutra notebook
that I use to feed my delusions.
SIGN: Sutra Notebook
SIGN: God
TAMON: This is impressive.
TAMON: You've written down things
that even I don't remember.
UTAGE: If we objectively re-evaluate your character,
it'll probably help you stay on track.
TAMON: You're right. I might just pull through
if I look through these.
UTAGE: Good. Now I'll also be able to participate
in the meet-and-greet in peace.
TAMON: Um...
UTAGE: Yes?
TAMON: I'm sorry to keep bothering you,
but could you help me do some simulations?
TAMON: For the meet-and-greet.
UTAGE: Huh?
UTAGE (INT): No, no, no! I couldn't enjoy
that kind of bliss for free!
TAMON: R-Right. Of course.
TAMON: It was presumptuous of a walking trash bag
like me to think I could take up your time.
UTAGE: Huh?
UTAGE: Hello? If it's for Tamon-kun, I could offer up
all my time in this lifetime and the next!
TAMON: Thank you very much.
UTAGE: Oh, whoops.
MUSHROOMS: Gloom, gloom.
UTAGE: Ahem.
UTAGE: I'll continue to support you.
UTAGE: Please keep doing your best.
TAMON: Don't worry.
TAMON: I'll never let you switch oshis.
TAMON: I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
TAMON: I grossed out Kinoshita-san to death!
UTAGE: The IRL version... is too OP.
TAMON: I don't want to keep seeing you
get hurt because of me, so I'll stop.
TAMON: I just keep relying on you... I'm so sorry.
UTAGE: Honestly, it makes me very happy.
TAMON: Huh?
UTAGE: You'd have no way of knowing this...
UTAGE: But when I was going through some hard times,
the one who was there to lift my spirits
UTAGE: more than anyone else was you, Tamon-kun.
UTAGE: So nothing makes me happier
than being able to help you out.
TAMON: Smooch.
UTAGE: Compared to everything you gave to me,
this is really nothing in return...
SIGN: Boom
UTAGE: But I'd give up my life to support you.
UTAGE: Agh!
SIGN: Boom
TAMON: I've wanted to meet you so badly.
Let's get married.
UTAGE: Tamon-kun...
UTAGE: If you use up all your energy now,
you're not going to last until the end.
TAMON: Hurgh!
UTAGE: Told you.
TAMON: It's so good...
TAMON: You're coming to the meet-and-greet too, right?
UTAGE: Yes! I'm going to give it my all!
TAMON: Then I'm hoping you can...
score how well I do.
UTAGE: Today, my oshi was once again a metronome.
UTAGE: My heartbeat is also a metronome.
UTAGE: Forever love... now and forever.
SIGN: The Day of the Meet-and-Greet
SIGN: Expensive gift
UTAGE: Wow... Wow, wow!
UTAGE: Everyone's so insanely hyped!
UTAGE: Tamon-kun, just look
at how many people love you!
RANDO GIRL: It's been so long, Tamon! How've you been?
TAMON: Hey, get over here.
TAMON: You're my girl, aren't you?
BG GIRL: Aah! Hello!
RANDO GIRL: Oh, my gosh! I can't!
RANDO GIRL: Tamon was exactly how I'd imagined him,
and he even made the air taste great.
TAMON: Hello.
RANDO GIRL B: I know, right?
RANDO GIRL B: He told me, "I love you!"
UTAGE: Thank goodness.
It sounds like he's doing just fine.
RANDO GIRL A: That's awesome, too!
UTAGE: Tamon-kun belongs to everyone.
RANDO GIRL B: I imploded for a second.
RANDO GIRL A: It was just too good.
UTAGE: Today's your oshi's day to shine.
Don't ruin it with your petty jealousy, Utage.
TROUBLEMAKER A: Ugh, what the hell?
TROUBLEMAKER A: You just totally stepped on my shoes
that I bought just for today.
TROUBLEMAKER B: It's your own fault
for trying to dance suddenly.
UTAGE: Trouble amongst fans?!
UTAGE: Hello?! Tamon-kun's right over there.
SIGN: Tamon Fukuhara
TROUBLEMAKER A: What do you have in that bag? Cookies?
TROUBLEMAKER A: Tamon won't like anything dry and crumbly.
TROUBLEMAKER B: What? I obviously know that.
UTAGE: I have to do something!
TROUBLEMAKER B: They're very moist, thank you very much.
UTAGE: Peacefully, peacefully...
SONG: (1) You're not gonna run now, are you?
UTAGE: Peace...
SONG: Ring that bell
SONG: Boom!!
UTAGE: Leave!
TROUBLEMAKERS: Huh?
TROUBLEMAKER B: Yer a Tamon oshi, too?
TROUBLEMAKER A: You want a piece of me?
UTAGE: Anyone who dirties Tamon-kun's
divine ears has no place in this world!
SIGN: Route
SIGN: No
cameras
GUARD: Hey! What are you arguing about?!
SIGN: F/ACE
SIGN: Meet-and-Greet
GUARD: You need to leave.
UTAGE: G-Goodbye, my paradise.
RANDO GIRL C: Tamon-kun's hand was so big and warm!
UTAGE: I mean, even if I don't get to go,
he's got plenty of passionate fans.
RANDO GIRL D: Yeah! He also held my hand so tight
that my heart started pounding!
UTAGE: As long as Tamon-kun's happy.
RANDO GIRL C: I'd love to go again.
RANDO GIRL D: We're going to have to keep supporting F/ACE!
UTAGE: I need to make up for my losses today.
SIGN: Meet
SIGN: Greet
UTAGE: There're no breaks in supporting your oshi.
UTAGE: Okay, gotta go to work.
SIGN: Housekeeping Made Easy
SIGN: Leave it to Us! Housekeeping Service
UTAGE: I'm back!
EMPLOYEE: Kinoshita-san! There's a guest for you.
UTAGE: Huh?
EMPLOYEE: Right over there.
UTAGE: What am I staring at right now?
IRL Photoshop?
TAMON: Why didn't you come?
UTAGE: I-I lost my ticket somewhere...
UTAGE: I did go all the way to the venue, though.
UTAGE: And then...
TAMON: You need to keep your promise.
TAMON: Ask me for anything.
TAMON: I'll respond.
UTAGE: This is...
UTAGE: This is a really presumptuous request...
UTAGE: I don't care if it's a lie.
Just let me continue dreaming.
UTAGE: Could you just become
my Tamon-kun just for a moment?
TAMON: No.
UTAGE: Huh?
MUSHROOM: Gloom.
TAMON: No! Not for just a moment!
UTAGE: Gloomyhara-san.
TAMON: I...
TAMON: I wanted to you to praise me, Kinoshita-san!
TAMON: So why'd you have to go and lose your ticket?
TAMON: I was waiting that whole time because
I wanted you to see the fruits of my labor...
TAMON: I wanted to make you happy...
TAMON: How could you...
SIGN: Squee Squee Squee
UTAGE: Ten billion points! Perfect score!
UTAGE: Deeper into the Tamon swamp I sink...
SIGN: Tokyo Municipal Hanagatani High School
SIGN: Tamon Meet-and-Greet
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Home
SIGN: Favorites
SIGN: Popular
SIGN: News
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Tamon Believer @tamonshinto99
SIGN: Our divine oshi in the flesh. Truly, a myth in the making.
SIGN: The fact that he exists at all is a service to us fans.
SIGN: #F/ACEMeetandGreet #F/ACEOFF
SIGN: #Tamon-kunIsGod
YUINA: Everyone at the meet-and-greet collectively
lost their minds, so it was hilarious.
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Tamon's Wife @tamonnotsumadesu...
SIGN: I guess you can physically touch the latest CG
SIGN: #F/ACEMeetandGreet
SIGN: #NoHumanCanBeBornThatPerfect
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Tamon's Mother @tamonmother1782
SIGN: He was just so perfect that I can't...
SIGN: He's literally god... Everyone he shook hands
SIGN: with before me imploded
SIGN: #F/ACEMeetandGreet #Tamon-kun
RIKO: The fandom is growing steadily.
YUINA: But I'm a little worried.
YUINA: If they're getting closer to their fans...
YUINA: What if our oshi ends up in a tabloid
for meeting some fangirl in private?
SIGN: Voluntary Hiatus From Activities
SIGN: A Close Look At Their Secret Night Together
He Took Her Right Home After Meeting A-san at a Mixer
RIKO: We're gonna murder that bitch.
YUINA: Yup, we sure are.
UTAGE: Huh?
UTAGE: W-Wait, what?!
RIKO: If any delusional girl
gets close to Tamon-kun...
YUINA: We'll murder her together!
YUINA/RIKO: Murder! Murder! Murder! Murder!
UTAGE: I can't tell them...
UTAGE: I can't tell them I'm casually
frequenting our oshi's home.
UTAGE: What happened this time?
TAMON: Well...
SIGN: Spontaneous
SIGN: Hot Guy Style
SIGN: Insanely
Hot
SIGN: Just Hot
SIGN: Sorta Lame
SIGN: Ultra Lame
MC: Do our popular hot guys
also normally dress hot?!
MC: We'll have our viewers go ahead
and rate these stylish celebrities!
UTAGE: Hey! This is the show
you're going to be on soon, isn't it?
MC: Spontaneous Hot Guy Style Check!
TAMON: Yes.
MC: Our victim this time is the morning drama
actor, Ikeo Iketeru-kun!
UTAGE: A super-popular variety show
that airs primetime on the weekends!
UTAGE: Congratulations!
TAMON: It's all over.
UTAGE: Huh?
TAMON: Please don't hate me or F/ACE!
TAMON: I'm so sorry these are the only clothes I own!
UTAGE: Oh, I guess this is the only thing
I've ever seen him wear.
UTAGE: But you look so great in that outfit.
UTAGE: Fans also wouldn't mind you not
having any fashion sense at all!
TAMON: Yes, you're right...
TAMON: Of course this worn-out, slightly-dirty,
lame hoodie would look perfect on me.
TAMON: No other outfit in this world
could possibly look good on me.
UTAGE: Could you actually listen to what I'm saying?
UTAGE: Hmm... I personally like the Gloomyhara look...
UTAGE: But we can't miss the opportunity
to show off his great physique.
UTAGE: Tamon-kun!
UTAGE: Let's go buy some clothes for you.
UTAGE: Please forgive me. But I'm sure you all
want to see a top-quality Tamon-kun!
TAMON: Sorry to keep you waiting.
UTAGE: How shockingly low-quality.
TAMON: Huh? Is there something weird about this?
UTAGE: No... As long as you're okay
with it, Gloomyhara-san.
UTAGE: Okay, let's go.
UTAGE: I remember all of the outfits
that Tamon-kun has worn up until now.
UTAGE: Which outfits were popular
and which ones weren't...
UTAGE: I'll use that info and my perspective
as a fan to come up with the ultimate look.
UTAGE: Let me make this clear:
UTAGE: I'm not fooling around here.
UTAGE: This is my duty as someone who represents
the Church of Tamon believers.
UTAGE: I'm opening up!
UTAGE: Did everything fit okay?
TAMON: It's perfect!
UTAGE: Hottiehara-kun has arrived!
TAMON: Look out, Kinoshita-san!
TAMON: If we're going to create some art,
a blank canvas is best.
SIGN: If we're going to
create some art,
a blank canvas
is best.
TAMON: Because my lifestyle
is the only pattern I need.
SIGN: Because my
lifestyle is the only
pattern I need.
TAMON: I can't let my guard down
just because I'm enjoying a day off.
TAMON: My existence is winning.
SIGN: My existence is winning.
SIGN: I am the rules.
TAMON: I am the rules.
TAMON: What do the ladies think? Like I care.
UTAGE: Tamon-kun's so eager to provide
fanservice that he's reflexively posing.
UTAGE: I wuv you.
UTAGE: What's the matter?
TAMON: I can't get this on...
MUSHROOM: Gloom.
TAMON: I'm so sorry that I'm such a
useless, talentless hack.
UTAGE: Who are you now?
TAMON: "Tamon-kun is actually human."
TAMON: I was somehow able to buy some clothes.
TAMON: Thank you so much.
UTAGE: You're very welcome.
TAMON: Do you come here often?
UTAGE: Yes, sometimes on my way home from school.
UTAGE: I'll come here to study
with my friends before a test...
UTAGE: Which is just an excuse.
UTAGE: We usually just end up chatting.
RANDO GUY 1: Nice kill, my dude!
RANDO GUY 2: Okay, let's go for a knockout.
RANDO GUY 3: Got it!
RANDO GUYS: Go! Go!
TAMON: I'm kinda jealous...
TAMON: I-I'm sorry! I shouldn't say stuff like that
when we didn't come here for fun!
UTAGE: It's okay. I was just admiring
that even someone as amazing as you
UTAGE: would enjoy the same things
us normal people like.
UTAGE: You don't go out with your groupmates?
UTAGE: Oh...
UTAGE: That... was loud and clear.
RIKO: Oh, hey. Isn't that Utage?
YUINA: It is! What're you doing here?
UTAGE: Oh, shit!
YUINA/RIKO: Murder! Murder!
UTAGE: Wh-What a coincidence!
YUINA: Who's that?
RIKO: That's a rather unique hat.
UTAGE: Um...
TAMON: I'm... her friend.
UTAGE: I just made our god lie
and humble his very existence!
UTAGE: Yeah... from middle school...
RIKO/YUINA: Oh, really...
RIKO: Wait, is he your boyfriend?!
UTAGE: Wait, no! No, no, no!
RIKO: Come on, just show us your face already.
UTAGE: No, really! He's not!
UTAGE: Please, just stop!
TAMON: Sorry, we're in a hurry!
RIKO/YUINA: Hey! They ran away!
UTAGE: This is... This is just...
UTAGE: a secret date!
UTAGE: I'm so terribly sorry!
TAMON: Huh? Why are you apologizing?!
UTAGE: This is an important time in your life,
yet I carelessly took you out,
UTAGE: and put you in danger of being
found by the paparazzi!
UTAGE: I'm unworthy of being your fan!
I deserve capital punishment!
TAMON: But I'm the one who asked you to help me.
TAMON: It's not right for you to apologize—
UTAGE: No!
UTAGE: Even if you forgive me, Tamon-kun,
I won't forgive myself.
TAMON: But I had fun—
UTAGE: From now on!
UTAGE: I'll do my best to stay at least
three meters away from you.
UTAGE: I'm so very sorry!
TAMON: Kinoshita-san, please look at me.
TAMON: Do you like me?
UTAGE: Of course I do? I have never felt anything
for you other than love and affection!
TAMON: Then you can shut up for a second
and listen to what I have to say, right?
TAMON: I had a lot of fun today. Thank you.
UTAGE: I see...
TAMON: Huh? Kinoshita-san?
UTAGE: A few days later, Tamon-kun's outfits
were praised for having a boyfriend look.
SIGN: The No. 1 guy you want as your boyfriend
SIGN: Tamon Fukuhara
SIGN: from F/ACE!!!
UTAGE: My oshi seems to be burnt to a crisp today.
TAMON: Oh, good evening.
UTAGE: This violates the
Cultural Properties Protection Law!
UTAGE: Restoring the national treasure!
SIGN: Splash Splash Splash
SIGN: Wipe Wipe Wipe Wipe
SIGN: Voooooooor Vooooooor
TAMON: I'm always making you do things
outside of household chores,
TAMON: so I figured I could try to cook
something for myself but...
UTAGE: What were you trying to make, exactly?
TAMON: A rolled omelet...
SIGN: Kill...
SIGN: me....
EGG: Kill... me... Kill... me...
Kill... me... Kill... me...
TAMON: Forget doing justice to a life
brought into this world,
TAMON: I ended up ruthlessly murdering it
and abandoning it.
UTAGE: Now, now, everyone struggles at first.
TAMON: I'm going on a voluntary hiatus from work
until I can properly fry an egg.
UTAGE: Wait a minute!
UTAGE: Even if you can't fry an egg,
UTAGE: there is something you're very good
at making, Tamon-kun!
UTAGE: Making your fans smile!
GIRLS: I love you! I love you!
UTAGE: You're able to make all those smiles!
SIGN: Church of Tamon
UTAGE: If that doesn't make you a top chef,
I don't know what does!
UTAGE: Have more confidence in yourself!
TAMON: I'm not sure if I fully understand,
but I somehow feel like I can keep going.
UTAGE: That's Fujita-san, his manager.
FUJITA: That was impressive.
FUJITA: You somehow immediately got Tamon
out of his nervous breakdown mode.
FUJITA: I'm shocked.
FUJITA: I never thought he'd be rehabilitated
this much just by hiring a housekeeper.
FUJITA: He's actually been
obediently working lately.
UTAGE: Well, household chores get
so tiresome when you're busy.
TAMON: Fujita-san, you just see me as a cash cow,
but Kinoshita-san doesn't.
TAMON: I don't think. Probably.
UTAGE: He looks like an abandoned puppy
that doesn't trust humans anymore.
FUJITA: By the way, just how much
counts as household chores?
UTAGE: Honestly, pretty much anything,
depending on the customer.
UTAGE: I even go shopping
or take pets out for a walk.
FUJITA: I see.
FUJITA: So practicing for the meet-and-greet
and going shopping together
FUJITA: counts as "household chores."
UTAGE: I'm so sorry!
UTAGE: One wrong move, and I could've
caused a huge misunderstanding!
TAMON: Kinoshita-san didn't do anything wrong!
TAMON: If you're going to kill someone, kill me!
FUJITA: Please continue helping with all of
Tamon's "household chores" from now on!
UTAGE: Huh?
FUJITA: This is embarrassing to admit, but we're
a small little agency with no connections.
FUJITA: We absolutely don't have enough people.
FUJITA: Honestly, you're a lifesaver!
FUJITA: Now, then... I have to go buy some
maritozzi for a certain selfish gorilla,
FUJITA: so take care of the
nervous breakdown zombie for me!
UTAGE: Um...
UTAGE: So basically... anything goes.
TAMON: I want you to accept all of me.
UTAGE: Personal desires... begone!
TAMON: Are you all right, Kinoshita-san?
UTAGE: Yes, I'm fine.
UTAGE: Calm yourself, Utage.
UTAGE: You're just helping Tamon-kun out
with his idol work.
TAMON: Please don't push yourself too hard.
UTAGE: When Tamon-kun was sixteen,
he came to Tokyo all alone for his audition.
UTAGE: From everything I've personally seen,
UTAGE: it seems like his manager's not
taking care of him that much.
UTAGE: He doesn't get along that well
with the other members either.
UTAGE: Of course he'd rely on a busybody fangirl
that just happened to come into his life.
UTAGE: Yes. I'm just a convenient fan to Tamon-kun.
UTAGE: Then I'm just going to have to work
my hardest so I don't let him down...
UTAGE: As the person in charge of household chores.
UTAGE: Oh, I wonder if it's from work...
UTAGE: A candid shot!
UTAGE: Oh, I'm sorry to yell like that
while you're working.
TAMON: It's fine.
TAMON: I was just thinking that you're
so interesting, Kinoshita-san.
UTAGE: Huh? Am I?
TAMON: Yes.
TAMON: You just suddenly yell sometimes.
UTAGE: All of your fans are like this.
TAMON: I don't know about anybody else. But...
TAMON: If anything, to me right now...
TAMON: You're special, Kinoshita-san.
UTAGE: Oh, come on!
UTAGE: Jeez, Tamon-kun.
UTAGE: He's just excellent at fanservice,
UTAGE: and he just happened to have
a fan right in front of him.
UTAGE: That's why he instantly says
stuff that makes me happy.
UTAGE: At first, I was just trying to escape reality.
FRIEND: You're so boring, Uta-chan.
UTAGE: Huh?
FRIEND: I'm the only one who ever
talks in our conversations.
FRIEND: It's good to accommodate others,
but that's all you ever do.
FRIEND: I have no idea what you're even thinking.
UTAGE: When I'd been flattened like an empty husk,
you just happened to cross my eye.
16 YEAR OLD TAMON: I want to make everyone in the world smile.
UTAGE: And you happened to say something I'd never
say even if I'd been reborn a hundred times.
UTAGE: An encounter with the unknown.
UTAGE: Ever since I learned of your existence,
every day's been so fun and going by so fast!
UTAGE: Your dream became my dream.
UTAGE: That's why I don't need to be special.
UTAGE: He looked at me!
UTAGE: You're special to me, so just
having you show me your dream...
UTAGE: Huh? That necklace...
UTAGE: ...makes me so happy.
UTAGE: Or so I thought...
UTAGE: Huh?
TAMON: You're special, Kinoshita-san.
UTAGE: What was that just now?
LYRICS: Uh huh...
LYRICS: Na na na...
LYRICS: I wonder what the world
would look like without you
LYRICS: When I look back,
you've always been by my side
LYRICS: Teaching me what "warmth"
and "happiness" feel like
LYRICS: A speedboat sails across the endless skies
LYRICS: An unwavering course,
a straight shot down the middle
LYRICS: An unbreakable red balloon
found nowhere else
LYRICS: Is this "fate"? Or just a "coincidence"?
LYRICS: Like a wilted flower coming back to life
LYRICS: A light that shines
LYRICS: Through the impossibly dark night
LYRICS: (Light of your soul)
LYRICS: I wanted to grasp it
LYRICS: (I love you so)
LYRICS: So I strived for it
LYRICS: Wanna keep going, wanna keep growing
LYRICS: Bringing our flowers and dreams
into full bloom